Inventory of the William J. Casey papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- PRIVATE LIFE FILE ADDENDUM, 1976-1981 (Boxes 507-544)
  - Subject file. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, studies, legal and financial records, and printed matter
    - Tri-Rotor Motor Company (Box-folder 542: 2-5)
    - Tri-Rotor Motor Company (contd.) (Box-folder 543: 1-2)
    - Union League Club (New York City) (Box-folder 543: 3)
    - University Club (Washington, D.C.) (Box-folder 543: 4)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. (Box-folder 543: 5-6)
    - W. L. Haines Company (Box-folder 544: 1)
    - Wackenhut Corporation (Box-folder 544: 2)
    - Wolf and Company (Box-folder 544: 3)
  - Clippings (Box-folder 544: 4)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 544: 5)
- REAGAN/BUSH CAMPAIGN FILE ADDENDUM, 1980 (Boxes 545-553)
  - Events
    - Republican National Convention, Detroit, Michigan, 1980 July 14-17 (Box-folder 545: 1)
      Programs, preparatory materials, and miscellany
    - Television debate between Ronald Reagan and Jimmy Carter, 1980 October 28 (Box-folder 545: 2)
      Preparatory materials
  - Correspondence
    - General (Box-folder 545: 3)
    - Cromwell, James H. R. (Box-folder 545: 4)
      Includes his pamphlet Ronnie le Cowboy
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 545: 5)
  - Campaign briefing books and handbooks
    Includes issue statements, memoranda and reference material
    - 1979 December (Box-folder 545: 6-7)
    - 1980 February (Box-folder 546: 1-2)
    - 1980 August (Box-folder 546: 3-4)
    - 1980 September (Box-folder 547: 1-2)
  - Schedules, 1980 April (Box-folder 547: 3)
  - Memoranda (Box-folder 547: 4)
  - Subject file. Briefing papers, memoranda and background materials
    - Apparel industry (Box-folder 547: 5)
    - Automobile and steel industries (Box-folder 547: 6)
    - Campaign strategy (Box-folder 547: 7)
    - Capital formation, innovation and productivity (Box-folder 547: 8)
    - Carter, Jimmy, and Carter administration
      - General (Box-folder 548: 1)
      - Abuse of office (Box-folder 548: 2)
      - Quotations (by Carter and other leading Democrats) (Box-folder 548: 3)
    - Congress and Congressional staff (Box-folder 548: 4)
    - Domestic issues (Box-folder 548: 5)
    - Eastern region personnel (Box-folder 548: 6)
    - Economic policy (Box-folder 549: 1)
    - Finance (Box-folder 549: 2)
    - Ford, Gerald R. (Box-folder 549: 3)
    - Foreign policy issues (Box-folder 549: 4)
    - Liability of campaign officials (Box-folder 549: 5)
    - Media
      - General (Box-folder 549: 6)
      - Editorial board meetings, 1980 June (Box-folder 549: 7)
    - Middle East (Box-folder 549: 8)
    - New York City and national urban policy (Box-folder 549: 9)
    - Republican Governors' Strike Force (Box-folder 550: 1)
    - Republican National Committee (Box-folder 550: 2)
    - Targeted audiences (Box-folder 550: 3)
    - Vice presidential candidate selection (Box-folder 550: 4)
  - Publicity. Press coverage re WJC (Box-folder 550: 5)
  - Press coverage of campaign (Box-folder 550: 6)
  - Press coverage of campaign (contd.) (Box-folder 551-552)
  - Notes (Box-folder 553: 1)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 553: 2)
  - Congratulatory letters on election outcome (Box-folder 553: 3-5)
  - Retrospective analyses of campaign (Box-folder 553: 6-7)
- PRESIDENTIAL TRANSITION TEAM FILE ADDENDUM, 1980-1981 (Boxes 554-556)
  - Events
    - New York State College of Electors meeting, Albany, 1980 December 15 (Box-folder 554: 1)
      Programs and correspondence
    - Presidential inauguration, Washington, D.C., 1981 January 20 (Box-folder 554: 2)
      Programs, commemorative book, and memorabilia
  - Pre-election transition planning materials (Box-folder 554: 3)
  - Correspondence (Box-folder 554: 4)
  - Memoranda (Box-folder 554: 5)
  - Office of Policy Coordination handbook and meeting schedules (Box-folder 554: 6)
  - Subject file. Reports and studies
    - Energy (Box-folder 554: 7)
    - Foreign policy. Includes Interim Foreign Policy Advisory Board materials (Box-folder 554: 8)
    - Government regulation and business relations. Report of the Business Advisory Panel of the Task Force on Government Regulation and Business Relations (Box-folder 555: 1)
    - Intelligence (Box-folder 555: 2)
    - International agencies. Report on Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, International Development Coordination Agency, international financial institutions, Board for International Broadcasting, and International Communication Agency (Box-folder 555: 3-4)
    - Presidential management. Report by a panel of the National Academy of Public Administration (Box-folder 555: 5)
    - Small Business Administration. Report of the Transition Team on the U.S. Small Business Administration (Box-folder 556: 1-2)
  - Notes (Box-folder 556: 3)
  - Press coverage (Box-folder 556: 4)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 556: 5)
- CENTRAL INTELLIGENCE AGENCY FILE ADDENDUM, 1981-1987 (Boxes 556-592)
  - Speeches and engagements. Correspondence, notes, memoranda, agenda, meeting and background materials, and press coverage. Speech transcripts are noted when present
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. dinner in honor of Margaret Thatcher, New York City, 1981 February 28 (Box-folder 556: 6)
    - Friendly Sons of St. Patrick dinner, New York City, 1981 March 17 (Box-folder 557: 1)
    - Center for International Business International Trade Conference, Dallas, Texas, 1981 April 9 (Box-folder 557: 2)
    - Chamber of Commerce annual meeting, Washington, D.C., 1981 April 28 (Box-folder 557: 3)
    - Department of State Executive Seminar in National and International Affairs, Washington, D.C., 1981 May 6 (Box-folder 557: 4)
    - Business Council annual meeting, Hot Springs, Virginia, 1981 May 9 (Box-folder 557: 5)
    - Financial Analysts Federation annual conference, Washington, D.C., 1981 May 12 (Box-folder 557: 6)
    - St. John's University commencement with honorary award to WJC, Brooklyn, New York, 1981 May 17 (Box-folder 557: 7)
    - World Business Council conference, Washington, D.C., 1981 May 20 (Box-folder 557: 8)
    - Fordham University Club dinner with award to WJC, Chevy Chase, Maryland, 1981 May 28 (Box-folder 557: 9)
    - Commencement exercises with award of honorary degree to WJC, Polytechnic Institute of New York, Brooklyn, 1981 June 3 (Box-folder 557: 10)
    - Commencement exercises with award of honorary degree to WJC, New York Law School, New York City, 1981 June 7 (Box-folder 557: 11)
    - St. John's University Alumni Association luncheon, Washington, D.C., 1981 June 11 (Box-folder 557: 12)
    - OER Free World briefing, 1981 June 30 (Box-folder 557: 13)
    - Central Intelligence Agency Senior Intelligence Service promotion ceremony, Washington, D.C., 1981 June 30 (Box-folder 557: 14)
    - Central Intelligence Agency employees meeting, Washington, D.C., 1981 July 27 (Box-folder 557: 15)
    - Fordham University alumni dinner, Fordham University, New York City, 1981 October 8 (Box-folder 557: 16)
    - John M. Olin Distinguished Lecture, Brown University, Providence, Rhode Island, 1981 October 15 (Box-folder 557: 17)
    - Yorktown Bicentennial celebration, Yorktown, Virginia, 1981 October 16-19 (Box-folder 557: 18)
      Includes reading by WJC excerpted from his book An Armchair Tour of the American Revolution
    - Special Forces Club meeting, London, England, 1981 October 23 (Box-folder 558: 1)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission annual awards ceremony, Washington, D.C., 1981 November 19 (Box-folder 558: 2)
    - Harvard Law School and Wellesley College Associations District of Columbia Chapters joint visit to the Central Intelligence Agency, Washington, D.C., 1981 December 1 (Box-folder 558: 3)
    - Pinay Cercle dinner, 1981 December 4 (Box-folder 558: 4)
    - Ronald Reagan first inaugural anniversary dinner dance, Washington, D.C., 1982 January 20 (Box-folder 558: 5)
    - Society of the Four Arts meeting, Palm Beach, Florida, 1982 February 23 (Box-folder 558: 6)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency annual student symposium, Washington, D.C., 1982 March 13 (Box-folder 558: 7)
    - St. Patrick's Day celebration, White House, Washington, D.C., 1982 March 17 (Box-folder 558: 8)
    - Republicans Abroad meeting, Washington, D.C., 1982 March 23 (Box-folder 558: 9)
    - President's Commission on Executive Exchange meeting, 1982 April 21 (Box-folder 558: 10)
    - White House Fellows meeting, Washington, D.C., 1982 April 30 (Box-folder 558: 11)
    - Business Council meeting, Hot Springs, Virginia, 1982 May 8 (Box-folder 558: 12)
    - Business-Government Relations Council meeting, Washington, D.C., 1982 May 11 (Box-folder 559: 1)
    - Association of Former Intelligence Officers meeting, San Francisco, California, 1982 May 21 (Box-folder 559: 2)
    - Commonwealth Club of California meeting, San Francisco, 1982 May 21 (Box-folder 559: 3)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. dinner in honor of John A. McCone, San Francisco, California, 1982 May 22 (Box-folder 559: 4)
    - White House Fellows meeting, Washington, D.C., 1982 June 2 (Box-folder 559: 5)
    - Council of the Americas meeting, Washington, D.C., 1982 June 3 (Box-folder 559: 6)
    - Anti-Defamation League appeal dinner in honor of James A. Finkelstein, New York City, 1982 June 3 (Box-folder 559: 7)
    - Commercial Law League of America meeting, Washington, D.C., 1982 June 14 (Box-folder 559: 8)
    - Retirement ceremony of Phil Loomis from Securities and Exchange Commission, Washington, D.C., 1982 June 24 (Box-folder 559: 9)
    - Smithsonian Resident Associate Program on Great American Battles of World War II: New Perspectives, Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C., 1982 July 15 (Box-folder 559: 10)
    - American Legion annual convention, Chicago, Illinois, 1982 August 24 (Box-folder 559: 11)
    - National Military Intelligence Association meeting, Washington, D.C., 1982 September 10 (Box-folder 559: 12)
    - American Business Conference annual meeting, Washington, D.C., 1982 September 29 (Box-folder 559: 13)
    - SIGNA Society meeting, 1982 October 7 (Box-folder 559: 14)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. reception for Dutch resistance delegation, Washington, D.C., 1982 October 7 (Box-folder 559: 15)
    - Business and labor leaders meeting, White House, Washington, D.C., 1982 October 25 (Box-folder 559: 16)
    - Robert K. Gray electoral victory celebration, Washington, D.C., 1982 November 4 (Box-folder 559: 17)
    - Harry J. Sievers Memorial Lecture, Center for the Study of the Presidency, New York City, 1982 November 17 (Box-folder 559: 18)
      Draft lecture
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency dinner in honor of Edwin Meese, Washington, D.C., 1983 February 2 (Box-folder 560: 1)
    - Sons of the American Revolution banquet, Palm Beach, Florida, 1983 February 21 (Box-folder 560: 2)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency National Defense Executive Reserve conference, Washington, D.C., 1983 March 7 (Box-folder 560: 3)
    - American Business Conference meeting, Washington, D.C., 1983 March 9 (Box-folder 560: 4)
    - Trip to Asia, 1983 March 25-April 11 (Box-folder 560: 5)
    - Edward Weintal Prize ceremony, Georgetown University, Washington, D.C., 1983 April 13 (Box-folder 560: 6)
    - Central Intelligence Agency Executive Seminar in National and International Affairs, Washington, D.C., 1983 April 21 (Box-folder 560: 7)
    - Junior Chamber of Commerce Arthur S. Flemming Awards ceremony, Washington, D.C., 1983 April 22 (Box-folder 560: 8)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. dinner in honor of Richard Helms, Washington, D.C., 1983 May 24 (Box-folder 560: 9)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. dinner in honor of Sir William Stephenson, New York City, 1983 September 22 (Box-folder 560: 10)
    - Dinner in honor of Leo Cherne, New York City, 1983 September 29 (Box-folder 560: 11)
    - John Findley Green Foundation Lecture, Westminster College, Fulton, Missouri, 1983 October 29 (Box-folder 560: 12)
      Lecture
    - Senate Select Committee on Intelligence hearings on establishment of a national historical intelligence museum, Washington, D.C., 1983 November 3 (Box-folder 560: 13)
      Transcript of testimony
    - American Foreign Policy Association dinner, Washington, D.C., 1983 November 30 (Box-folder 560: 14)
    - Commonwealth Club of California luncheon, Palo Alto, 1984 April 3 (Box-folder 561: 1)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace dinner, Stanford University, Stanford, California, 1984 April 3 (Box-folder 561: 2)
    - Mid-America Committee dinner, Chicago, Illinois, 1984 April 4 (Box-folder 561: 3)
    - White House correspondents dinner, Washington, D.C., 1984 April 13 (Box-folder 561: 4)
    - Commencement exercises, Bryant College, Providence, Rhode Island, 1984 May 19 (Box-folder 561: 5)
    - Jedburgh reunion, Paris, France, 1984 May 29-June 1 (Box-folder 561: 6)
    - Jubilee reunion, Fordham University, New York City, 1984 June 8-10 (Box-folder 561: 7)
    - American Stock Exchange conference, Washington, D.C., 1984 June 12 (Box-folder 561: 8)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission anniversary dinner, Washington, D.C., 1984 June 29 (Box-folder 561: 9)
    - Citizens for America meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 July 11 (Box-folder 561: 10)
    - D-Day landing anniversary celebration, Toulon, France, 1984 August 15 (Box-folder 561: 11)
    - Rotary Club meeting, Seattle, Washington, 1984 September 26 (Box-folder 561: 12)
    - Association of Former Intelligence Officers convention, Rockville, Maryland, 1984 October 20 (Box-folder 561: 13)
    - Central Intelligence Agency memorial service for employees killed in El Salvador airplane crash, Washington, D.C., 1984 October 29 (Box-folder 561: 14)
    - Pumpkin Papers Irregulars Halloween banquet, Washington, D.C., 1984 October 31 (Box-folder 561: 15)
    - Association of Former Intelligence Officers meeting, New York City, 1984 November 2 (Box-folder 561: 16)
    - Fordham University alumni meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 November 14 (Box-folder 561: 17)
    - Intelligence Community Awards Ceremony, Washington, D.C., 1984 December 7 (Box-folder 561: 18)
    - Dinner in honor of E. Pendleton James, 1984 December 11 (Box-folder 561: 19)
    - Union League Club meeting, New York City, 1985 January 9 (Box-folder 561: 20)
    - Central Intelligence Agency National Black History Month Observance program, Washington, D.C., 1985 February 7 (Box-folder 561: 21)
      Introduction of Carl T. Rowan
    - Time Update on America '85 meeting, Washington, D.C., 1985 February 26 (Box-folder 561: 22)
    - Submarine Birthday Ball, Arlington, Virginia, 1985 April 13 (Box-folder 561: 23)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy National Security Studies Program conference, Tufts University, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1985 April 17 (Box-folder 561: 24)
    - World Affairs Council meeting, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1985 April 29 (Box-folder 561: 25)
    - Metropolitan Club meeting, New York City, 1985 May 1 (Box-folder 561: 26)
    - World Business Council conference, San Antonio, Texas, 1985 May 18 (Box-folder 561: 27)
    - Conference on Economic and Security Implications of Structural Change, Washington, D.C., 1985 June 3 (Box-folder 561: 28)
    - Central Intelligence Agency University Placement Directors' Conference, Washington, D.C., 1985 June 27 (Box-folder 561: 29)
    - Meeting with business leaders, Detroit, Michigan, 1985 July 18 (Box-folder 561: 30)
    - Security Affairs Support Association meeting in honor of Barry Goldwater, Washington, D.C., 1985 July 30 (Box-folder 561: 31)
    - Central Intelligence Agency career trainee graduation ceremony, Washington, D.C., 1985 August 13 (Box-folder 561: 32)
    - Advisory Commission on Public Diplomacy meeting, Washington, D.C., 1985 September 10 (Box-folder 562: 1)
    - Council on World Affairs meeting, Dallas, Texas, 1985 September 18 (Box-folder 562: 2)
    - Central Intelligence Agency Conference on Liberation Theology and Communism, Washington, D.C., 1985 September 19 (Box-folder 562: 3)
    - Stanford Research Institute and Center for Strategic and International Studies Symposium on Terrorism and Industry, Washington, D.C., 1985 October 14 (Box-folder 562: 4)
    - Senate Committee on the Judiciary hearings on the nomination of Stanley Sporkin for a federal judgeship, Washington, D.C., 1985 October 29 (Box-folder 562: 5)
    - Wedding of Bernadette Casey (daughter of WJC) and Owen T. Smith, Old Westbury, New York, 1985 December 7 (Box-folder 562: 6)
    - Central Intelligence Agency award ceremony for Edward P. Boland, Washington, D.C., 1985 December 16 (Box-folder 562: 7)
    - Christmas reception, WJC residence, Washington, D.C., 1985 December 20 (Box-folder 562: 8)
    - Central Intelligence Agency presentation of Distinguished Intelligence Medal to Stanley Sporkin, Washington, D.C., 1986 February 19 (Box-folder 562: 9)
    - Swearing-in ceremony of Stanley Sporkin as judge of the District Court for the District of Columbia, Washington, 1986 February 21 (Box-folder 562: 10)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency Harry J. Sievers Lecture, Fordham University, New York City, 1986 February 25 (Box-folder 562: 11)
    - National Defense University Armed Forces Staff College lecture, Norfolk, Virginia, 1986 March 21 (Box-folder 562: 12)
    - Council of American Ambassadors meeting, Washington, D.C., 1986 April 3 (Box-folder 562: 13)
    - American Israel Public Affairs Committee Policy Conference, Washington, D.C., 1986 April 6 (Box-folder 562: 14)
    - American Society of Newspaper Editors meeting, Washington, D.C., 1986 April 9 (Box-folder 562: 15)
    - Association of Former Intelligence Officers National Intelligence Symposium, Naples, Florida, 1986 May 5 (Box-folder 562: 16)
    - Commencement exercises, C. W. Post College, Long Island University, New York, 1986 May 11 (Box-folder 562: 17)
    - American Jewish Committee annual meeting, Washington, D.C., 1986 May 15 (Box-folder 562: 18)
    - Meeting with business leaders, Atlanta, Georgia, 1986 May 24 (Box-folder 562: 19)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. dinner in honor of Ronald Reagan, Washington, D.C., 1986 May 29 (Box-folder 562: 20)
    - Central Intelligence Agency ceremony and exhibition in honor of William J. Donovan, Washington, D.C., 1986 June 2 (Box-folder 563: 1)
    - Society for Historians of American Foreign Relations annual meeting, Georgetown University, Washington, D.C., 1986 June 25 (Box-folder 563: 2)
    - Rocky Mountains College Placement Association meeting, Snowmass, Colorado, 1986 July 30 (Box-folder 563: 3)
    - Meeting with business leaders, Denver, Colorado, 1986 July 30 (Box-folder 563: 4)
    - Howard Taft Lecture, University Club, Washington, D.C., 1986 September 18 (Box-folder 563: 5)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. and William J. Donovan Foundation OSS/Donovan Symposium, Washington, D.C., 1986 September 19 (Box-folder 563: 6)
    - Society of Professional Journalists meeting, Washington, D.C., 1986 September 24 (Box-folder 563: 7)
    - Washington Times Advisory Board and Editorial Board annual meeting, Washington, D.C., 1986 September 25 (Box-folder 563: 8)
    - National Security Agency new building dedication, Fort Meade, Maryland, 1986 September 26 (Box-folder 563: 9)
    - John M. Ashbrook Center for Public Affairs Lecture, Ashland College, Ashland, Ohio, 1986 October 27 (Box-folder 563: 10)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency conference luncheon, Atlanta, Georgia, 1986 November 8 (Box-folder 563: 11)
    - Southern Center for International Studies meeting, Atlanta, Georgia, 1986 November 8 (Box-folder 563: 12)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. reunion, Bangkok, Thailand, 1986 November 9-23 (Box-folder 563: 13)
    - Practising Law Institute Communications Law Conference, New York City, 1986 November 14 (Box-folder 563: 14)
    - Testimonial dinner for Robert C. Ames, La Salle University, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1986 December 11 (Box-folder 563: 15)
  - Correspondence
    - A-P (miscellaneous) (Box-folder 563: 16)
    - Best, William H. (Box-folder 563: 17)
    - Bush, George (Box-folder 563: 18)
    - Casey, George L. (Box-folder 564: 1)
    - Collins, John J. (Box-folder 564: 2)
    - Cuneo, Ernest (Box-folder 564: 3)
    - Durenberger, David F. (Box-folder 564: 4)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Box-folder 564: 5)
    - Hugel, Max (Box-folder 564: 6)
    - Hymoff, Edward (Box-folder 564: 7)
    - Irvine, Reed (Box-folder 564: 8)
    - Juncker, Flemming (Box-folder 564: 9)
    - Landau, Ralph (Box-folder 564: 10)
    - McCone, John A. (Box-folder 564: 11)
    - McKinnon, Dan (Box-folder 564: 12)
    - Morris, Robert (Box-folder 564: 13)
    - R (Box-folder 564: 14)
    - Rabb, Maxwell M. (Box-folder 564: 15)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 564: 16)
    - Regan, Donald T. (Box-folder 564: 17)
    - Regnery, Henry (Box-folder 564: 18)
    - Rendell, Robert S. (Box-folder 564: 19)
    - Reynolds, Alan (Box-folder 564: 20)
    - Ricardo-Campbell, Rita (Box-folder 564: 21)
    - Richardson, John (Box-folder 564: 22)
    - Riff, Michael (Box-folder 564: 23)
    - Robinson, Roger W., Jr. (Box-folder 564: 24)
    - Romanones, Aline, Condesa de (Box-folder 564: 25)
    - Ronsac, Charles (Box-folder 564: 26)
    - Rosenbaum, Joseph H. (Box-folder 565: 1)
    - Rosenthal, A. M. (Box-folder 565: 2)
    - Rosselli, Jean-Pierre (Box-folder 565: 3)
    - Rostow, Eugene V. (Box-folder 565: 4)
    - Rostow, W. W. (Box-folder 565: 5)
    - Rowny, Edward L. (Box-folder 565: 6)
    - Rusher, William A. (Box-folder 565: 7)
    - Rynne, Donald (Box-folder 565: 8)
    - S (Box-folder 565: 9)
    - Safire, William (Box-folder 565: 10)
    - Sanders, Sol W. (Box-folder 565: 11)
    - Sandler, Roger (Box-folder 565: 12)
    - Schiffer, Robert M. (Box-folder 565: 13)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur, Jr. (Box-folder 565: 14)
    - Schmidt, Adolph W. (Box-folder 565: 15)
    - Scott, Harold B. (Box-folder 565: 16)
    - Seabury, Paul (Box-folder 565: 17)
    - Seehusen, Svenn (Box-folder 565: 18)
    - Selin, Ivan (Box-folder 565: 19)
    - Shad, John S. R. (Box-folder 565: 20)
    - Shaheen, John and Michael (Box-folder 565: 21)
    - Shipley, Carl (Box-folder 565: 22)
    - Simon, William E. (Box-folder 565: 23)
    - Sirica, John J. (Box-folder 565: 24)
    - Six, Robert F. (Box-folder 565: 25)
    - Smith, Earl E. T. (Box-folder 565: 26)
    - Smith, Owen T. (Box-folder 565: 27)
    - Smith, William French (Box-folder 565: 28)
    - Sommer, A. A., Jr. (Box-folder 566: 1)
    - Sønsteby, Gunnar (Box-folder 566: 2)
    - Spitzer, Arthur (Box-folder 566: 3)
    - Sporkin, Stanley (Box-folder 566: 4-6)
    - Stans, Maurice H. (Box-folder 566: 7)
    - Stephenson, William, Sir (Box-folder 566: 8)
    - Sternfield, Lawrence (Box-folder 566: 9)
    - Stivers, T. E. (Box-folder 566: 10)
    - Strausberg, Marc (Box-folder 566: 11)
    - Strausberg, Marc (contd.) (Box-folder 567: 1)
    - Sugahara, Kay (Box-folder 567: 2)
    - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs (Box-folder 567: 3)
    - T (Box-folder 567: 4)
    - Taylor, Richard P. (Box-folder 567: 5)
    - Theberge, James D. (Box-folder 567: 6)
    - Thornburg, James F. (Box-folder 567: 7)
    - Thurmond, Strom (Box-folder 567: 8)
    - Titus, David L. (Box-folder 567: 9)
    - Tofte, Hans (Box-folder 567: 10)
    - Turner, Stansfield (Box-folder 567: 11)
    - Tuttle, Holmes (Box-folder 567: 12)
    - Tyrrell, R. Emmett, Jr. (Box-folder 567: 13)
    - Ullman, Harlan K. (Box-folder 567: 14)
    - V (Box-folder 567: 15)
    - Viscardi, Henry, Jr. (Box-folder 567: 16)
    - W (Box-folder 567: 17)
    - Walkowicz, T. F. (Box-folder 567: 18)
    - Wallace, Mike (Box-folder 567: 19)
    - Wanniski, Jude (Box-folder 567: 20)
    - Watt, James G. (Box-folder 567: 21)
    - Webster, William H. (Box-folder 568: 1)
    - Weidenfeld, Edward L. (Box-folder 568: 2)
    - Welchman, Gordon (Box-folder 568: 3)
    - West, Nigel (Box-folder 568: 4)
    - White, Peter (Box-folder 568: 5)